The one who went dark will shine brighter than comets
Passing over the planet
From the void, without your beauty, youth's free bird will not be born.
Fly above the Earth
Like an eagle, like an eagle
Shine above the Earth
Like fire, like fire
The one who has lost will love again
Beyond the dawn, eternal summer draws near
Through the night till dawn, you keep your bird safe in your soul.
Don't let it crash
Fly above the Earth
Like an eagle, like an eagle
Shine above the Earth
Like fire, like fire
Planet Earth, this is Captain Adams on the Serenity.
We're receiving a repeated message from the Martian surface.
Do you read me?
Fly above the Earth
Like an eagle, like an eagle
Shine above the Earth
Like fire, like fire
Planet Earth, this is Captain Adams on the Serenity.
We're receiving a repeated message from the Martian surface.
Do you read me?